Guide to the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, Yale University, Student Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Student grade lists, circa 1932-1975; Accession 2005-A-048
  - Biology -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 202)
  - Chemistry -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 203)
  - Chemistry -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 204)
  - Chemistry -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 205)
  - Physics -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 206)
  - Physics -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 207)
  - Physiology -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 208)
  - Physiology -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 209)
  - Physiology -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 210)
  - Political Science -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 211)
  - Political Science -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 212)
  - Political Science -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 213)
  - Portuguese -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 214)
  - Portuguese -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 215)
  - Psychology -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 216)
  - Spanish -A Term, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 217)
  - Spanish -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 218)
  - Statistics -A Term, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 219)
  - Statistics -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 220)
  - Statistics -Full Term, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 221)
  - Other Grades -1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 222)
  - Undergraduate -A Term, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 223)
  - Undergraduate -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 224)
  - Law School -A Term, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 225)
  - Law School -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 226)
  - History -A Term, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 227)
  - History -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 228)
  - Slavic -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 229)
  - Law School -1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 230)
  - Geology -A Term, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 231)
  - Geology -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 232)
  - Geology -Full Term, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 233)
  - German -A Term and Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 234)
  - German -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 235)
  - History of Art -A Term and Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 236)
  - History of Art -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 237)
  - History of Theater -A Term and Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 238)
  - History of Science and Medicine -A Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 239)
  - History of Science and Medicine -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 240)
  - History of Science and Medicine -Full Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 241)
  - Institute of Social Science -A Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 242)
  - Institute of Social Science -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 243)
  - Institute of Social Science -Full Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 244)
  - Italian -A Term and Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 245)
  - Italian -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 246)
  - Linguistics -A Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 247)
  - Linguistics -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 248)
  - Mathematics -A Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 249)
  - Mathematics -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 250)
  - Mathematics -Full Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 251)
  - Philosophy -A Term and Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 252)
  - Philosophy -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 253)
  - Pharmacology -A Term and Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 254)
  - Pharmacology -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 255)
  - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures A Term and Full Year, 71-1972 (Box 5, Folder 256)
  - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 257)
  - Music -A Term and Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 258)
  - Music -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 259)
  - Molecular Biochemistry and Biophysics -A Term and Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 260)
  - Molecular Biochemistry and Biophysics -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 261)
  - Microbiology -A Term and Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 262)
  - Microbiology -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 263)
  - Medieval Studies -A Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 264)
  - Medieval Studies -Full Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 265)
  - Physics -A Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 266)
  - Physics -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 267)
  - Physics -Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 268)
  - Microbiology -A Term and Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 269)
  - Microbiology -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 270)
  - Physiology -A Term and Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 271)
  - Physiology -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 272)
  - Political Science -A Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 273)
  - Political Science -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 274)
  - Political Science -Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 275)
  - Portuguese -A Term and Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 276)
  - Portuguese -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 277)
  - Psychology -A Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 278)
  - Psychology -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 279)
  - Psychology -Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 280)
  - Religious Studies -A Term and Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 281)
  - Religious Studies -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 282)
  - Slavic -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 284)
  - Sociology -A Term and Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 285)
  - Sociology -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 286)
  - Southeast Asian Studies -1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 287)
  - History of Art -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 288)
  - Classics -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 289)
  - Classics -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 290)
  - Classics -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 291)
  - Comparative Literature -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 292)
  - Comparative Literature -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 293)
  - Comparative Literature -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 294)
  - Computer Science -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 295)
  - Computer Science -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 296)
  - Computer Science -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 297)
  - East Asian Studies -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 298)
  - East Asian Studies -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 299)
  - East Asian Languages and Literatures -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 300)
  - East Asian Languages and Literatures -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 301)
  - East Asian Languages and Literatures -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 302)
  - Economics -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 303)
  - Economics -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 304)
  - Economics -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 305)
  - Engineering -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 306)
  - Engineering -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 307)
  - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 308)
  - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 309)
  - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 310)
  - Physics -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 311)
  - Physics -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 312)
  - Physics -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 313)
  - Physiology -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 314)
  - Physiology -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 315)
  - Physiology -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 316)
  - Political Science -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 317)
  - Political Science -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 318)
  - Political Science -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 319)
  - Psychology -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 320)
  - Pharmacology -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 321)
  - Pharmacology -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 322)
  - Mathematics -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 323)
  - Medieval Studies -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 324)
  - Medieval Studies -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 325)
  - Microbiology -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 326)
  - Microbiology -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 327)
  - Microbiology -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 328)
  - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 329)
  - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 330)
  - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 331)
  - Music -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 332)
  - Music -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 333)
  - Music -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 334)
  - English -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 335)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 336)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 337)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 338)
  - Geology and Geophysics -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 339)
  - Geology and Geophysics -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 340)
  - Geology and Geophysics -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 341)
  - Germanic Languages and Literatures -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 342)
  - Germanic Languages and Literatures -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 343)
  - Germanic Languages and Literatures -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 344)
  - History of Art -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 345)
  - History of Art -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 346)
  - History of Art -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 347)
  - History of Science and Medicine -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 348)
  - History of Science and Medicine -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 349)
  - History of Science and Medicine -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 350)
  - History of the Theatre -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 351)
  - History of the Theatre -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 352)
  - History of the Theatre -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 353)
  - Human Genetics -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 354)
  - Human Genetics -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 355)
  - Human Genetics -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 356)
  - I.S.P.S. -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 357)
  - I.S.P.S. -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 358)
  - I.S.P.S. -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 359)
  - Linguistics -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 360)
  - Linguistics -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 361)
  - Mathematics -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 362)
  - Mathematics -Full Year Term, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 363)
  - Pharmacology -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 364)
  - Philosophy -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 365)
  - Philosophy -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 366)
  - Philosophy -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 367)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health -A Term, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 368)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health -B Term and Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 369)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies -A Term and Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 370)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 371)
  - French -A Term and Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 372)
  - French -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 373)
  - Administrative Sciences -A Term, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 374)
  - Administrative Sciences -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 375)
  - Administrative Sciences -Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 376)
  - American Studies -A Term and Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 377)
  - American Studies -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 378)
  - Anatomy -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 380)
  - Anthropology -A Term, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 381)
  - Anthropology -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 382)
  - Anthropology -Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 383)
  - Biology -A Term, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 384)
  - Biology -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 385)
  - Biology -Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 386)
  - Chemistry -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 387)
  - Chemistry -Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 388)
  - Astronomy -A Term, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 389)
  - Astronomy -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 390)
  - Astronomy -Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 391)
  - Chemistry -A Term, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 392)
  - Classics -A Term and Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 393)
  - Classics -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 394)
  - Comparative Literature -A Term and Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 395)
  - Comparative Literature -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 396)
  - Computer Science -A Term, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 397)
  - Computer Science -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 398)
  - Computer Science -Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 399)
  - East Asian Languages and Literatures -A Term and Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 400)
  - East Asian Studies -B Term, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 401)
  - Economics -Full Year, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 402)
  - Psychology -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 403)
  - Psychology -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 404)
  - Political Science -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 405)
  - Political Science -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 406)
  - Political Science -1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 407)
  - History of Art -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 408)
  - History of Art -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 409)
  - History of Art -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 410)
  - History -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 411)
  - History -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 412)
  - History -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 413)
  - Philosophy -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 414)
  - Philosophy -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 415)
  - Philosophy -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 416)
  - History of the Theatre-B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 417)
  - History of the Theatre -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 418)
  - History of Science and Medicine -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 419)
  - History of Science and Medicine -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 420)
  - History of Science and Medicine -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 421)
  - Human Genetics -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 422)
  - Human Genetics -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 423)
  - Human Genetics -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 424)
  - Institution for Social and Policy Studies -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 425)
  - Institution for Social and Policy Studies -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 426)
  - Institution for Social and Policy Studies -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 427)
  - Italian -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 428)
  - Italian -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 429)
  - Italian -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 430)
  - Law School -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 431)
  - Physics -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 432)
  - Physics -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 433)
  - Physics -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 434)
  - Physiology -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 435)
  - Physiology -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 436)
  - Physiology -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 437)
  - Political Science -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 438)
  - Classics -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 439)
  - Classics -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 440)
  - Classics -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 441)
  - Comparative Literature -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 442)
  - Comparative Literature -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 443)
  - Comparative Literature -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 444)
  - Computer Science -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 445)
  - Computer Science -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 446)
  - Computer Science -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 447)
  - East Asian Languages and Literatures -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 448)
  - East Asian Languages and Literatures -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 449)
  - East Asian Studies -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 450)
  - East Asian Studies -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 451)
  - East Asian Studies -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 452)
  - Economics -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 453)
  - Economics -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 454)
  - Economics -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 455)
  - Engineering and Applied Science -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 456)
  - Engineering and Applied Science -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 457)
  - Engineering and Applied Science -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 458)
  - Germanic -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 459)
  - Germanic -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 460)
  - Law School -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 461)
  - Engineering and Applied Science -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 462)
  - English -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 463)
  - English -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 464)
  - English -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 465)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 466)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 467)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 468)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 469)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 470)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 471)
  - French -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 472)
  - French -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 473)
  - French -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 474)
  - Geology and Geophysics -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 475)
  - Geology and Geophysics -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 476)
  - Geology and Geophysics -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 477)
  - Psychology -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Psych. 169-230) (Box 9, Folder 478)
  - Psychology -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Psych. 241-260) (Box 9, Folder 479)
  - Religious Studies -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 480)
  - Religious Studies -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 481)
  - Religious Studies -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 482)
  - Portuguese -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 483)
  - Portuguese -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 484)
  - Portuguese -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 485)
  - Slavic -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 486)
  - Slavic -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 487)
  - Music -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 488)
  - Music -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 489)
  - Music -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 490)
  - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 491)
  - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 492)
  - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 493)
  - Pharmacology -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 494)
  - Pharmacology -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 495)
  - Pharmacology -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 496)
  - Linguistics -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 497)
  - Linguistics -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 498)
  - Linguistics -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 499)
  - Mathematics -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 500)
  - Mathematics -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 501)
  - Mathematics -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 502)
  - Microbiology -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 503)
  - Microbiology -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 504)
  - Microbiology -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 505)
  - Medical School -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 506)
  - Medical School -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 507)
  - Medical School -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 508)
  - Medieval Studies -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 509)
  - Medieval Studies -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 510)
  - Russian -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 511)
  - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 512)
  - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 513)
  - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 514)
  - Miscellaneous Professors -Letter F -1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 515)
  - Administrative Sciences -, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 516)
  - American Studies -, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 517)
  - Anatomy -, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 518)
  - Anthropology -, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 519)
  - Astronomy -, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 520)
  - Biology -, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 521)
  - Economics -, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 522)
  - Chemistry -, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 523)
  - Classics -, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 524)
  - Comparative Literature -, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 525)
  - East and South Asian Languages and Literatures -, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 526)
  - Engineering and Applied Science (1stTerm) -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 527)
  - Engineering and Applied Science (2ndTerm) -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 528)
  - English -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 529)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 530)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 531)
  - Geology and Geophysics -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 532)
  - German -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 533)
  - History -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 534)
  - History of Art -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 535)
  - History of Science and Medicine -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 536)
  - History of Theatre -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 537)
  - Linguistics -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 538)
  - M.A.T. -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 539)
  - Mathematics -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 540)
  - Medieval Studies -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 541)
  - Microbiology -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 542)
  - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 543)
  - Music -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 544)
  - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 545)
  - Pharmacology -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 546)
  - Physics -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 547)
  - Physiology -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 548)
  - Political Science -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 549)
  - Portuguese -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 550)
  - Philosophy -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 551)
  - Psychology -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 552)
  - Religious Studies -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 553)
  - Italian -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 554)
  - Slavic Languages and Literatures -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 555)
  - French -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 556)
  - Spanish -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 557)
  - Sociology -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 558)
  - Statistics -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 559)
  - Extensions -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 560)
  - Other Schools -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 561)
  - Miscellaneous Grades that have been Recorded to File -, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 562)
  - Miscellaneous Grades, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 563)
  - Miscellaneous Grades, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 564)
  - Miscellaneous Grades, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 565)
  - Romance Languages -, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 566)
  - Anatomy -, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 567)
  - American Studies -A Term, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 568)
  - American Studies -B Term, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 569)
  - American Studies -Full Year, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 570)
  - Anatomy -A Term, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 571)
  - Anatomy -B Term, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 572)
  - Astronomy -1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 573)
  - Anthropology -1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 574)
  - Biology -1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 575)
  - Chemistry -1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 576)
  - Classics -A Term, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 577)
  - Classics -B Term, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 578)
  - Classics -Full Year, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 579)
  - Comparative Literature -A Term, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 580)
  - Comparative Literature -B Term, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 581)
  - Comparative Literature -Full Year, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 582)
  - Computer Science -1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 583)
  - East and South Asian Studies -A Term, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 584)
  - East and South Asian Studies -B Term, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 585)
  - East and South Asian Studies -Full Year, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 586)
  - Economics -1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 587)
  - Engineering and Applied Sciences -1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 588)
  - English -A Term, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 589)
  - English -B Term, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 590)
  - English -Full Year, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 591)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health -A Term, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 592)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health -B Term, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 593)
  - Forestry -A Term, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 594)
  - Forestry -B Term, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 595)